Hello, it's been a while since we both met.
こんにちは、2人とも久しぶり
How have you been?
元 気してた?
These two were friends.
この2人、友達だったんだね
It's nice to have such a beautiful friend.
こんな美人な友達、いいな
We can be proud of each other, right?
お互い自慢できるでしょ?
I agree.
そうですね
What does it have to do with it?
何の関係なの?
We work part-time at the same place.
バイト先が一緒です
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
I wonder where I can meet you,
どこに行ったら会えるんだろうね、
To such cute children.
こんな可愛い子たちに
I went to see the cherry blossoms today.
今日桜見に行ったね
I went to cherry blossom viewing and other things.
花見したことし、それ以外で
first time.
初
first time?
初?
Yeah, first time.
うん、初
how was it?
どうだった?
Look at the cherry blossoms.
桜見って
It was beautiful.
綺麗だった
You don't really go to cherry blossom viewing, do you?
お花見はあんまりしないんだ?
normally.
普段
Don't you go with your friends from school?
学校のお友達とか行かないの?
Don't go to cherry blossom viewing, young children.
お花見行かないんだ、若い子たちは
I see
なるほど
hey.
ね
They're both wearing cute clothes.
2人 とも可愛い服着てるね
Is it always like that?
いつもそういう感じ?
As for clothes.
服は
You wear black, Sakura-chan.
黒とか着るんだね、桜ちゃん
I'll wear it.
着ます
It suits you.
似合うね
Are you nervous today?
今日緊張してる?
Really.
めっちゃ
Do you really want to do it?
めっちゃする?
My friends are going to see me naked today.
友達に裸見られちゃうね、今日
Have you ever shown it?
見せたことある?
do not have.
ない
That's a little exciting too.
ちょっとそこもドキドキだね
Awkward?
気まずい?
a little bit.
ちょっと
We're good friends, both of us.
仲いいしね、2人ともね
Both of you stand up.
2人とも立ってこな
The screen has amazing destructive power.
すごい破壊力だよ、画面が
This one is cute too.
こっちも可愛い
Well then, let's both take the lead for a moment.
じゃあちょっと2人とも、主体になってみようか
Can you take it out slowly?
ゆっくり抜いてもらえる?
Adults are amazing, their necks are amazing.
大人さんすごいね、首レが
That's an amazing neck.
ものすごい首レだ
Erotic.
エロ
People will call you erotic when you walk around town.
街歩いててエロって言われるでしょ
I've never been told that.
言われたことない
Have you ever been told that?
言われたことないか
So cute, both of you.
可愛いね、2人とも
Kuro-chan, what do you think of this body?
黒ちゃんどうですか、この体
That's sexy.
セクシーですね
Kuro-chan, are you nervous?
黒ちゃん緊張してる?
I'm really nervous.
めっちゃ緊張してる
No way.
まさか
This picture is erotic.
エロいよな、この絵は
He has a great face and says nice things.
すげえ顔いいこと言ってる
Well then, let's start with Sakura-chan.
じゃあちょっとさくらちゃんから、
Shall I take a picture of your bra?
ブラ撮ってみようか
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Shall I show you my master?
オーターちゃん見せちゃう?
What kind of breasts do you have?
どんなおっぱいしてるか
It's so beautiful.
すごい綺麗だよね
So beautiful.
めっちゃ綺麗
This boobs.
このおっぱい
I think mirrors are cute myself, right?
自分でも鏡って可愛いって思うだろ、
this.
これ
If only it were this beautiful.
こんなに綺麗だったら
You definitely think so.
絶対思うでしょ
Eh, Roy boobs.
えー、ロイおっぱい
The shape is erotic.
形がエロいね
Next is Auto-chan.
次はオーターちゃん
Let's take a picture of my bra.
ブラ撮ってみよう
What do you think, Kura-chan?
どうですか、このくらちゃん
The shape is so beautiful.
形めっちゃ綺麗
The two best people are here.
最高の2人が、そろいましたよ、ここに
The shape of both of them is already extremely erotic.
2人とも形がもう、めちゃくちゃエロいんだよな
Those are boobs that don't seem to be used at all.
全然使ってなさそうなおっぱいだね
The shape is so beautiful.
そんなに形が綺麗ってこと
The color is also very pink.
色もすごいピンクだしね
Look at each other's boobs.
お互いのおっぱい見てみて
copper?
どう?
beautiful.
綺麗
綺 麗
It's just beautiful, isn't it?
普通に綺麗なんだよな、もう
Now, turn around, both of you.
じゃあ、後ろ向いて、2人とも
Keep your hair a little forward.
髪ちょっと前にしておく
Look at me, both of you.
こっち向いてみて、2人とも
Just the face.
顔だけ
That's amazing.
すげーな
Well then, Sakura-chan, turn this way.
じゃあ、さくらちゃん、こっち向いて
Auto-chan, try taking this off.
オーターちゃん、これ脱がしてみて
pants?
パンツ?
Try taking off your friend's pants.
友達のパンツを脱がしてみて
Take a look.
見てみて
Eh, smooth.
え、ツルツル
That's erotic
エロいな
ah.
ぁ
Sakura-chan, next.
さ くらちゃん、次
Very beautiful hair.
めっちゃ毛が綺麗
Sakura-chan, this is your leg.
さくらちゃん、こっちの足さ
Try putting it next to you.
そばに置いてみて
Shoulders and legs.
肩足
Auteur-chan also does it.
オーターちゃんもやって
This leg.
こっちの足さ
They're both looking great.
2人ともすごい格好してるんだよ
Then, follow the body movements.
そしたら次、その体操作に沿って
Both of you should open it at the same time.
2人同時に開いてこな
They're both really cute
2人ともマジで可愛いんだ
Yo.
よ
amazing.
すごい
Open it with your own hands.
それ 自分の手で開いてこな
Open it.
開いてこな
That's a beautiful pussy.
綺麗なおまんこだね
The color is amazing pink.
色がすげえピンク
Sakura-chan opened it too.
さくらちゃんも開いて
Next, get on all fours.
次、4つんぼになって
Gah gah gah.
ギャーギャーギャー
So, I pushed my ass backwards with my legs.
で、思いっきりお尻すぎ足で後ろにプリンって
Look at this too.
こっちも見て
Kuro-chan and this friend.
くろちゃんとこの仲間
Highest.
最高
Highest?
最高?
Kuro-chan, hold your butt.
くろちゃん、お尻持ってさ
Spread your pussy open.
おまんこ広げてあげて
Your butt has great elasticity.
お尻の弾力がすごいね
I'm so curvy.
プリプリしてるよ
Open more.
もっと開いて
Otowa-chan.
おとわちゃん
Let me touch your chest a little.
くりちょっと触ってあげて
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ?
Are you embarrassed in front of your friends?
友達の前だと恥ずかしい?
Yeah, it's embarrassing.
うん、恥ずかしい
But that's cute.
でもそれが可愛いよ
It's Sakura-chan's pussy.
さくらちゃんのおまんこだね
Sakura-chan, look here.
さくらちゃんこっち見て
Kuro-chan, hands.
くろちゃん、手
delicious?
おいしい?
Kuro-chan.
くろちゃん
Let me be crispy.
くりぴんぴんにさせてあげて
Kuro-chan, Otowa-chan.
くろちゃん、おとわちゃん
Let me get you wet.
ぬれぬれにしてあげて
This butt too.
こっちのお尻も
Both are delicious, right?
どっちもおいしいでしょ?
Kuro-chan.
くろちゃん
Yeah, it's delicious.
うん、おいしい
You can lick every corner.
すみすみは舐めていいよ
Can you put one foot in here?
ここに片っぽい足乗っけられる?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Pussy.
おまんこ
Yeah, it feels good.
うん、気持ちいい
Do you like being licked?
舐められるの好き?
Yeah.
うん
Kuro-chan and Sakura-chan's pussies.
くろちゃん、さくらちゃんのおまんこ
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Pussy.
おまんこ
I was sitting right in front of them, just like the other two.
2人と同じで正面に座って
Kuro-chan, please sit in the middle.
くろちゃん、この真ん中に座ってください
Please sit down.
座ってください
It's here.
ここだね
Pengo, maybe.
ペンゴか、ちょっと
Take them both.
2人とも持ってよって
Kuro-chan.
くろちゃん
Don't lick my nipples.
乳首ペロペロしないで
Don't smoke too much.
いっぱい吸ってないで
Sakura-chan, here.
さくらちゃん、ここ
Please make sure you are sucking the nipple.
乳首吸ってるところにしてください
Put it all in your mouth.
口の中に全部入れて
copper?
どう?
Kuro-chan.
くろちゃん
Both of them just kept looking down and being careful.
2人ともそのまま下に向けて注意していって
Well then, Sakura-chan.
じゃあ、さくらちゃん
Please wet your pants.
パンツ濡らしてください
Kuro-chan, I think you're already excited.
くろちゃん、もう興奮しちゃったってんじゃん
Sakura-chan, touch the tip.
さくらちゃん、先っぽ触って
It's here, just touch it by chance.
ここだじゃん、たまたま触って
Try squeezing both of them.
2人ともギュッてみて
Give me a jerk.
シコシコしてあげて
How do you feel when you look at Chin Chin?
チンチン見るとどういう気分になる?
I feel naughty.
エッチな気分になる
Sakura-chan too?
さくらちゃんも?
Please do it faster
もっと早くしてあげ
hand.
て
Well then, let's both have Chin Chin, and then both of us can revote.
じゃあ 2人でチンチン持って、2人でリボートでやんな
Give it a jerk at the same time.
同時にシコシコしてあげて
What's going on Chin Chin?
チンチンどうなってる?
hard.
硬い
Sakura-chan, please do it from below.
さくらちゃん、下からペロンってやって
It's Perron.
ペロンって
First, give it a chew.
まず、チューしてあげて
How about your friend, don't lick my dick?
お友達はチンチン舐めてないで、どう?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Yeah.
うん
But you like it when I don't lick it, don't you?
でもチンチン舐めないと好きでしょ?
Eat lots of hogoto.
いっぱいほうごと食べてこら
different?
違う?
My friends are licking me.
お友達は舐めてる
Sakura-chan happens to be licking me.
さくらちゃん、たまたま舐めてる
My friends are chin chin.
お友達はチンチン
Put it all in your mouth.
全部口に入れてこら
Chinchin delicious?
チンチン美味しい?
Yeah.
うん
It's starting to click, Peron-chan.
カ チカチになってきたね、ペロンちゃん
Does Peron feel good?
ペロン気持ちいい?
This time, two people took turns.
今度2人交代し
Sakura-chan is licking.
さくらちゃん舐めてる
Lick it until it moves properly?
ちゃんと動くまで舐める?
Reach out your hand.
手を伸ばして
Licking while flickering.
チカチながら舐める
Sakura-chan, please make my cock more sticky.
さくらちゃん、もっとチンチンをベタベタにしてあげて
Then, the two of us licked each other from the sides to the top.
そして2人で横から上までペロンで舐め合って
Lick it all up.
全部舐めつくして
I lick all the flakers too.
フラッカーも全部舐めるんだよ
Please make my dick harder.
チンチンもっと硬くしてあげて
Sakura-chan, please give me more peron.
さくらちゃん、もっとペロンを出してくれ
Lick them both.
2人とも舐めて
Sakura-chan, speak.
さくらちゃん、喋って
If you like, talk.
好 きな方、喋って
Shouldn't we just play around?
ついでとか、遊ぶしじゃない?
If you like it, let me talk.
好きな方、喋らせて
Sakura-chan, does it feel good?
さくらちゃん、気持ちいい?
I hit it hard.
ガンバンついちゃって
My mouth is full.
口の中、パンパンだよ
Finally, the two of us rode together.
最後、2人で乗って
Chin Chin, I'm sorry.
チンチン、ごめんなさい
Highest.
最高
Shall we tease two people in bed?
ベッドに2人いじめるか?
Shall we do that?
そうしようか
Lick them both.
2人とも舐めて
Kuro-chan, shall I lick them both?
くろちゃん、2人とも舐めちゃおうか
Shall we do that?
そうしようか
Go get some sleep, right there.
ちょっと寝てごらん、そこに
It's okay, Kuro-chan.
いいよ、くろちゃん
From above as you like.
上から好きなように
This is the best style.
最高のスタイルだね、これ
Kuro-chan, showing off her pussy.
くろちゃん、おまんこ見せながら
Dad, show me your pussy.
お父さん、おまんこ見せて
Sakura-chan, open it.
さくらちゃん、開いて
Show off
見せつけとこ
To.
に
You're doing a naughty pose.
エ ッチなポーズしてるね
Your pussy is completely visible.
おまんこ丸見えだよ
Kuro-chan, let's play with some toys.
くろちゃん、ちょっとおもちゃでじめようか
Shall we do that?
そうしようか
Have you both been on the phone before?
2人とも電話やったことあるでしょ?
Let's just guess each other,
ちょっとお互いにさ、当ててみてよ、
all.
全部
can?
できる?
Pussy, stop it.
おまんこ、やめて
Make your friend's pussy feel good.
友達のおまんこ、気持ちよくして
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It's cute.
かわいいよ
It's twitching.
ひくひくしてるね
Does it feel good there?
そこ気持ちいいの?
feeling
気持
Good.
ち いい
It feels good, so close your legs.
気持ちいいって、足閉じてきて
I feel like it's going to be fine.
ちゃんといいそうな気持ち
Does it feel good?
くる気持ちいい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Hold on to your limits.
限界まで我慢していってね
Kuro-chan, you need to wear your breasts more.
くろちゃん、もっとおっぱいはめしなきゃね
Sakura-chan, please let me go.
さくらちゃん、いかせてごらん
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It feels good.
気 持ちいい
I'm going to expand the whole thing.
全体を広めていくね
Sakura-chan, you let me go.
さくらちゃん、いかせちゃったね
Just look at my pussy.
いったまんこ見して
Kuro-chan, open it.
くろちゃん、開いて
Is it open when you reach the back?
奥までたったら開いてる?
Have you never done anything like this?
こんなにしたことない?
do not have.
ない
Please make yourself feel good.
い っぱい気持ちよくしてね
Does it feel good to come?
くる気持ちいいの?
Just call me.
ちょっと呼び出して
This needs to have proper breasts.
これ、ちゃんとおっぱいしなきゃね
Just be patient and go.
我慢してから行くんだよ
Kuro-chan.
くろちゃん
Should I use that?
あれ使うか
秘密劇
Yagoto-chan, why don't you come in here?
やごとかちゃん、こっちに入れば?
Put it in.
入れて
It's handy.
手ついからね
cleaning club.
掃除クラブ
This is hitting me.
これぶつかってるよ
Do you understand?
わかる?
Have you ever done this yourself?
これ自分でもってやったことある?
Kuro-chan, I have no choice.
くろちゃん、仕方ないといけない
Seriously, look at it.
まじでごらん
A huge pussy.
めっちゃなまんこ
Does it feel good there?
そこ気持ちいいの?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Show me a lot.
いっぱい見せて
The stickers are coming down.
シールたられてきてるよ
I'm so blunt, right away.
こんなぶっかりなんだよ、さっそく
I'm starting to feel tired.
なんかたられてきちゃう
Yago.
やご
I guess there was a feeling.
気持ちがあったんだな
Kuro-chan.
くろちゃん
Do you want me to suck it again?
またしゃぶらせるか?
Shall we do that?
そうしようか
That's what you're doing, Kugo-chan.
そうしてる、くごちゃん
Suck Yagoto-chan.
やごとかちゃんしゃぶってこ
It was a gab.
ギャブだったな
Get on top of Kugo-chan and make him six.
くごちゃんの上に乗ってシックスにして
Sakura-chan.
さくらちゃん
It's ticking, dick.
カチカチだね、ちんちん
Let's suck Sakura-chan too.
さくらちゃんも一緒にしゃぶらしてこ
Leave it alone, okay?
ふっといてしょ?
Sakura-chan also sucks my dick.
さくらちゃんもちんこしゃぶって
Kugo-chan also licked me a lot.
くごちゃんもいっぱい舐めてあげて
I agree with you.
たりとも一致だね
Make yourself feel good.
いっぱい気持ちよくして
Well, next time, Kugo-chan.
じゃあ今度、くごちゃん
Come on up.
上に来てこら
Sakura-chan, sleep below.
さくらちゃん下に寝て
Kugo-chan higher up.
く ごちゃんもっと上に
Kugo-chan, please chew my butt too.
くごちゃんもお尻チューしてこ
Kugo-chan harder.
くごちゃんもっと激しく
Kugo-chan is also intense at the end.
くごちゃん最後も激しく
Okay.
いいよ
Don't you want to say it soon?
そろそろ言いたいんじゃないの?
That's what I say.
それ自分で言うとこ
can?
できる?
Can be done
でき
Ru.
る
copper?
どう?
Chi-chiha?
ち んちは?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
big?
大きい?
big.
大きい
You can taste my hard dick all over.
固いちんちいっぱい味わっていいよ
Sakura-chan, everyone is coming in from behind.
さくらちゃん、後ろからみんな入ってると
child.
こ
My friend's pussy is full.
お 友達のまんこいっぱい入ってる
Erotic?
エロい?
Look how big your penis is.
ちんち大きいほら
I happen to be touching it.
た またま触ってるの
Shake me a lot of sperm.
精子いっぱい振ってあげて
Can you make an M shape on it?
その上でM字できる?
Look where my dick is.
ちんち入ってるとこ見してみて
I've never heard a female voice.
女声聞いたことない
Kugo-chan, please try to get up.
くごちゃん、起き上がってみて
Annoying.
うざいして
Chew with Kugo-chan and Sakura-chan.
くごちゃん、さくらちゃんとチューして
Sakura-chan, look from here.
さくらちゃん、こっちから見てごらん
Look carefully.
よく見てごらん
Spread your legs wider.
も っと足広げて
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
this.
これ
She's got a great pussy.
すんごくまんこいってるよ
Try lifting your hips more, then.
もっと腰を浮かしてみん、じゃあ
Lift your hips.
腰を浮かしてごらん
I'll follow you as hard as I can from below.
下から思いっきりついてあげるから
Sakura-chan, more.
さくらちゃん、もっと
Is your dick getting hard?
ちんちん硬くていっちゃった?
I'm gone.
いっちゃった
Look again.
もう一回見して
It's small and feels good, Kugo-chan.
狭くて気持ちいいね、くごちゃん
Next, let's put Sakura-chan's clothes on.
次、さくらちゃんのもんこいれよ
Here, I'm going to Yotsubai.
こっち、よつんばいに行くよ
Look where the dick is.
ちんちん入ってるとこ見てごらん
tight?
きつい?
Kugo-chan.
くごちゃん
Use this one for your butt.
こっちのお尻向けでよつんばいを
Push it all the way to the bottom.
一番奥までブッスンして
Just give it a try.
とりあえずやってみ
Just go there, both of you.
二人でもそっち行ってよ
Put your hand on that window and turn your butt towards me.
そこの窓のとこに手ついて、お尻こっち向けて
Enter from Sakura-chan.
さくらちゃんから入れて
Stick your butt out as hard as you can.
お尻を思いっきりプリッとつき出して
Does it look like it's going to go away?
いっちゃいそう?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Mainly
おも
Hey, it's full of dicks.
ん こ、ちんちんでいっぱいだね
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Come with more.
もっといっぱいついて
Kugo-chan, you still have to be patient.
くごちゃん、まだ我慢だ
Kugo-chan, don't pull out yet.
くごちゃん、まだ抜かない
It's all.
全部だし
I returned without a break.
休まずに戻った
Shall we go?
行こうか
Shall we do that?
そうしよっか
With such a cute voice.
こんな可愛い声で
hey.
ね
It was served.
出されちゃったね
It's slimy on my chest.
胸にぬるぬるしてる
I'll bring you roses.
バラいってくよ
Manju is tired.
まんじゅうだるけじゃん
Kugo-chan, I'll follow you deeper.
くごちゃんもっと奥までついてやる
When you are active.
せいじょういでいると
Where does it feel good?
どこが気持ちいい?
Because it feels good.
だって気持ちいい
Do you like the back?
奥が好きなの?
Yeah, I like it.
うん、好き
Kugo-chan, look.
くごちゃん、ほら
I'll get to the bottom of the gap.
隙の奥ついてやる
It's deep inside Chinchin.
ちんちんの奥つきなのや
My pussy is narrow so it's barely there.
おまんこ狭いからギリギリだな
Spread your legs all at once and see.
もう一気に足を広げて、ほら
Place it where it stings.
刺さってるところにして
It's slimy.
ぬるぬるしてるんだよ
I'm still patient.
まだ我慢だ
Do you want to put it out?
出したい?
already.
もう
I can hold back.
我慢できてる
I'm still holding back.
まだ我慢してる
Finally, let's go to the back.
最後、奥ついて行かしておこう
Push it out all at once.
もう一気に奥出して
Deep inside.
奥な奥
Deepest.
一番奥
I'm selling a lot at Rikin right now.
今、リキンでいっぱい出してます、
sperm.
精子
Did it come out like this on the second shot?
2発目でこんなに出たの?
It felt so good.
すっごい気持ちよかった
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
It felt so good.
すっごい気持ちよかった
Fill your pussy with cum.
おまんこいっぱい精子塗ってあげなさい
Both of you, please lick my dick clean.
これ2人ともさ、 ちんちん2人舐めてキレイにしてくれよ
The two of them have a lot of sperm in their buns.
2人のまんじると精子いっぱいついてるから
Did it look nice earlier?
さっきのキレイできた?
Well, it's already stopped.
じゃ、もう止まっちゃった
The last two.
最後2人で
Did both of you come out clean?
2人ともキレイにできた?
How was it for both of you?
2人ともどうだった?
Because it felt good.
気持ちよかったから
Thumpy with my first friends.
初の友達とサムピー
I was nervous.
緊張した
Were you nervous?
緊張した?
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
Both of them are so cute and I said "Wow".
2人ともすんげえ可愛くてすんげえ言っちゃったよ
Thank you.
ありがとうね
Shall we hide and play again?
また隠れて遊ぼう?
Thank you for today.
今日はありがとう